### PERSONAL INFORMATION

# Jeyanthi Selvaraj



Kohfurth 38C, 22850, Norderstedt

+49 152 24186320

ieyanthi226@gmail.com

LinkedIn: Jeyanthi-Selvarai/

Sex Female | Date of birth 02/06/1998 | Nationality Indian | Work permit Valid existing work permit (EU)

### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Goal oriented passionate individual with experience in user interface, databases, backend development, testing and debugging processes. Able to effectively self-manage during independent projects as well as collaborate in a team setting. My teammates would describe me as a determined, highly motivated individual who is always willing to learn.

**TECHSTACK** 

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Knockout js, AJAX, jquery, C# .NET, Oracle, SQL Open to learn and work with new technologies

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### Jul 2020 - May 2022

### Software Developer/Analyst

Deloitte, Hyderabad (India)

- As an analyst was part of a team that transitioned their applications from a legacy UI to newer technologies like Angular and physical databases to cloud
- Took over an application and handled all the development items and bug fixes
- Worked on critical production tickets for clients and the integrated applications on a daily basis
- Implemented a middleware messaging service to replace the existing API's between integrated applications
- Served as a point of contact for the team's everyday activities on Azure dashboards, CI/CD pipelines and releases

#### Jan 2020 - Jun 2020

### Software Developer Intern

Deloitte, Hyderabad (India)

- As a software developer intern supported a team that specialized in maintenance of highlevel production traffic
- Trained in Azure DevOps to support team's everyday activities
- Member of the department's employee engagement program called the 'Happiness Team'

#### Nov 2019 - Dec 2019

#### Student Intern

BHEL, Vellore (India)

- Acquired knowledge on how the IT department integrates all the highly hardware-based production areas
- · Created a simple easy to use application for their inventory department

#### **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

#### April 2023 - Present

### M.Sc.Digital Transformation Management

SRH University of Applied Sciences, Hamburg (Germany)

### July 2015 - June 2020

## M.Tech in Software Engineering

Vellore Institute of Technology, Vellore (India)

- · Graduated with a 9.0 CGPA
- A core committee member at VIT's Trekking club for two years and The director of operations and relations for a year
- Served as a volunteer at E-Ride an NGO

Page 1/2

Curriculum Vitae Jeyanthi Selvaraj

### PERSONAL SKILLS

### Languages

- Tamil Native proficiency
- English Full professional proficiency
- Telugu Full verbal proficiency
- German A2 Level

#### **Tools and Software**

- Microsoft Office<sup>TM</sup> Tools (Word, PowerPoint, Excel, Outlook)
- OS Windows, Mac
- Visual Studio, Visual Studio Code
- Azure DevOps, Jira
- Figma
- Postman
- · Rational Rose

### Hobbies and Interests

- Painting and Doodling (Instagram: asunflowersaesthetic/)
- Trekking

#### **REFERENCES**

### 1. G. Padma Lakshmi

Senior Analyst

Deloitte

Mindspace Rd, P Janardhan Reddy Nagar, Gachibowli, Hyderabad, Telangana 500032, India

Email: padmg@deloitte.com

Tel: +91 9003233691

## 2. G.D. Suresh Kumar

Manager

Deloitte

Mindspace Rd, P Janardhan Reddy Nagar, Gachibowli, Hyderabad, Telangana 500032, India

Email: gdsureshkumar@deloitte.com

Tel: +91 9000711598